{"data":[{"question":"Idaho ranks first among the states in potatoes production.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"ranks ","b":"among ","c":"in ","d":"potatoes ","answer":"4","explain":"- Potatoes-> potatoe","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"The decay of a muon is an example of an weak interaction between atomic particles.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"decay ","b":"an example ","c":"an weak ","d":"atomic particles","answer":"3","explain":"- An weak-> a weak","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"All village or tribe of the North American Indian confederacy had its annual green corn dance, a festival in which social'' ties were renewed.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"All ","b":"annual ","c":"a festival ","d":"social ","answer":"1","explain":"- An-> each","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Pipelines are continually inspected for leaks and for damage caused by such conditions as freezing temperatures, heavy rain, and soil erode.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"for damage ","b":"as freezing temperatures","c":"heavy rain","d":"soil erode","answer":"4","explain":"- Soil erode->soil erosion","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Plastics used to make textiles can be drawn into fine threads, them woven or knit into fabrics.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"can be drawn ","b":"fine threads","c":"woven ","d":"knit ","answer":"4","explain":"- Knit-> knitted","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Numerous types of cells, such as skin cells and white blood cells, have the power reproduce asexually.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Numerous","b":"such as","c":"white blood","d":"power reproduce","answer":"4","explain":"Verry Good! Correct\n\n- Power reproduce-> power to reproduce","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Although ferns lack flowers, they do have leaves, stems, and root.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Although","b":"lack","c":"do","d":"root","answer":"4","explain":"Verry Good! Correct\n\n- Root-> roots","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Crazy Horse is generally recognized for his courageous and skill, and he was revered by the Sioux as their greatest leader.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"generally recognized","b":"courageous and skill","c":"by","d":"greatest","answer":"2","explain":"Verry Good! Correct\n\n- Courageous and skill-> courage and skill","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Since a hospital is organized to protect and treat people who are ill, its goals,structures, and functions depend on the currently state of medical science.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is organized","b":"structures","c":"depend on","d":"currently","answer":"4","explain":"Verry Good! Correct\n\n- Currently-> current","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Small distinctions among stamps, unimportant to the person average, would mean a great deal to the stamp collector.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Small distinctions","b":"the person average,","c":"mean","d":"to","answer":"2","explain":"Verry Good! Correct\n\n- The person average-> the average person","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"}]}